ANDRIY NOSOV

1





FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Ternopil, Ukraine | REMOTE



+38(067) 909 86 40



nosovandriy@gmail.com



andriynosov.com

HARD SKILLS

- Javascript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS
- React, NextJS
- SCSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, MUI
- NPM. Babel. Redux. Rest API
- Git, Github, VSCode, Chrome Dev Tools, Vercel
- Figma, Jira, SEO, UX/UI
- English Intermediate (B1)

In my recent commercial projects, I preferred **NextJS**. This framework has integrated Image Optimization, handy Routing, and SSR which improves performance and SEO.

Also, I applied **TypeScript, Tailwind, Redux toolkit, and Axios.** I implemented the ability to receive order data in the Telegram bot, integrated the Facebook chat and Google Analytics service.

EDUCATION

Master's degree in Computer Engineering | 2005 - 2010

Ternopil Ivan Puluj National Technical University

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

Mate ccademy Frontend development

- Learned the fundamental stack of front-end technologies:
- Practiced workflow: working with Git and GitHub in a team, solving tasks and debugging, deploying web pages to a server;
- Implemented a lot of projects that are based on the latest technological stack: TypeScript, React, Redux.

ABOUT ME

As a frontend developer, I have a master's degree in computer engineering and experience with a stack of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Rest API and others. Now I continue to self-study and learn the backend stack.

My English level is Intermediate. I have good communication skills, which I acquired from a previous job where I worked on a large team and communicate with many clients.

I have good self-learning skills, for example, I have set up export possibilities in the company, without having any skills in this area.

I also worked on export documents, which allowed the company to increase its sales and enter the world market. So I can add responsibility and attentiveness to my strong point.

EXPERIENCE

2022-2023 - PROJECTS

• Logistic company (NextJS, TS, HTML, CSS, SCSS)

ראַ מולא

Todo App (React, TS, HTML, CSS, SCSS, REST API)

Route Table (React, TS, HTML, React Router, REST API)

ראַ 🕜

Employees Table (JS, HTML, CSS, SCSS)

• Dia website (HTML, CSS, SCSS)

• Bakery website (HTML, CSS, SCSS)

OTHER PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2013-2020 – Sales Manager (SE Chortkivskyi KHP)

- Traded grains and wheat flour in Ukraine:
- Implemented the export functionality abroad, which allowed exporting products to countries such as Azerbaijan, China, Moldova, and EU countries;
- Prepared export documents and delivered about 10 thousand tons of goods.

2010-2012 — Hardware Sales Manager (Tetra Consulting)

- Worked with product vendors;
- Bought and sold computer hardware and other related equipment;
- Signed cooperative agreements with new suppliers and expanded the dealer network.

2008-2010 — Computer Repair Technician (Tetra Consulting)

- Diagnosed and repaired computer hardware:
- Built and configured at least 500 PCs.